const quiz = [
  {
    question:
      "Which HTML5 element should contain important links for navigating a website?",
    options: ["li", "ul", "header", "nav"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which HTML5 element should contain important information about what page you are on and the topic of the page?",
    options: ["li", "ul", "header", "nav"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which JavaScript variable declaration is used when the assigned value is likely to change?",
    options: ["let", "var", "variable", "const"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which term in JavaScript can be used to describe a declared variable that has not yet been given a value?",
    options: ["null", "undefined", "typeError", "NaN"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which selector could refer to an html element with the class of 'sm-col'?",
    options: ["#sm-col", ".sm, .col", "[class~=col]", ".sm_col"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Setting an element height to '10vh' bases the height calculation on _________",
    options: [
      "viewfinder height",
      "viewport width",
      "visible height",
      "viewport height",
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which HTML5 property can be for custom data?",
    options: ["data", "data-custom", "custom-data", "custom"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which HTML5 tag is used to define 'independent, self-contained content' within a web page?",
    options: ["section", "article", "aside", "div"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following snippets does not result in a return value of 8?",
    options: ["8**1", "Math.pow(16, .75)", "2 * 2 * 'two'", "2**+'3'"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these statements is NOT true about browser-side JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "JavaScript can be used for functional programming.",
      "JavaScript can be used for file reading and writing on client machines.",
      "JavaScript does not require frameworks or libraries to be used.",
      "Though not class-based, JavaScript is an Object-Oriented Programming Language.",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the BEST??",
    options: ["You", "Me", "Us", "Them"],
    answer: 1,
  },
];
